<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mine Mapper 3</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Mine Mapper 3</string>
    <string name="dialog_message"><justify><b>About Mine Mapper 3.0</b>
            \n\nThe Mine Mapper App, designed and developed by an experienced geologist with over 30 years in the field, caters to the specific needs of geologists and mining engineers in the mining sector. It serves as a valuable Android application for tasks related to mineral administration, including the collection of field data and the verification of mining-related information provided by miners.
 While initially intended for geologists, this versatile app is accessible to a wider audience, enabling anyone using an Android device to efficiently gather point, line, and polygon data directly from the field. Version 3.0 brings substantial improvements, including the introduction of geotagged photos, a clinometer for slope measurements, and comprehensive map creation capabilities for points, lines, and polygons. Essentially, this app functions as a Geographic Information System (GIS) tailored for geologists working within the mining sector.

        </justify>

       \n\n <b>Developer Information</b>:\n\n
•	<b>Developer Name</b>: Biju Sebastian\n
•	<b>Previous Positions</b>: Senior Geologist/ Deputy Director (Department of Mining and Geology, Government of Kerala)\n
•	<b>Current Address</b>: Kunnamkott House, Manakad PO, Kerala, India, Pin: 685608\n
•	<b>Developer Email</b>: bsebastian@gmail.com\n
•	<b>Contact Number</b>: +91 9447310771\n
•	<b>Feedback Email</b>: theminemapper@gmail.com\n
•	<b>Website</b>: www.minemapper.in\n
        •	<b>Release Date</b>: 17th September 2023\n\n<justify><b>Disclaimer</b>\n\nThe Mine Mapper App is provided for preliminary mapping purposes only. While every effort has been made to ensure accuracy, the developer accepts no responsibility for inadvertent errors or omissions. The responsibility for the use of this application and the interpretation of its output lies solely with the user.

For precise and accurate mapping, it is recommended to employ professional-grade equipment such as Differential Global Positioning System (dGPS) devices. The Mine Mapper App should not be used as a substitute for such professional-grade tools in critical or high-stakes applications.

By using this app, you agree to the terms of this disclaimer.

        </justify>
    </string>
</resources>
