<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mine Mapper 2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Mine Mapper 2</string>
    <string name="dialog_message">
                \n<justify><b>What is the use of this App?</b>\n\nEven though this is a general-purpose app, the same has been developed to help the
Geologists during the field work (personal digital assistant). Using this app, one can do
the following:\n
1. Create a KML file by inputting coordinates of the boundary pillars of a quarry/mine\n
2. Create a KML file by capturing the location where you stand. This function is
developed for mapping the boundary pillars of mine or for capturing the boundary pillars
of illegal mining area etc. Make sure that the accuracy shown while capturing the
coordinates is around 3 m.\n
3. View distance between pillars and area of the map created using this app\n
4. Take field notes while conducting field work\n
5. Load KML files generated in KOMPAS app. Send the KML file to mobile and open the
file using Mine Mapper.\n
6. This App will help you to check whether the boundary pillars are erected as per the
coordinates provided by the mineral concession applicant /concession holder. You can
also identify whether the pillar position has been changed later by the concession
holder.\n\n<b>How to use this app?</b>\n\nCreate a map\n\nA KML file can be created by clicking Create Map button. There are two options to
create a map- by inputting coordinates in the degree: minutes: seconds or by capturing
the location of the coordinates. Buttons are provided to delete a pillar or edit the
coordinates of pillar. As you capture the coordinates of the pillar, the same will be
displayed along with the distance from one pillar to another. As soon as you capture a
minimum of three pillars, area of the polygon is also displayed in ha, sq.m and acre. The
accuracy of the GPS while capturing the pillar coordinates is also recorded for
reference.\n\nView a map\n\nAfter creation of the map, the map will be saved in the mine mapper folder of your
phone. You may not be able to view the saved map if you view the same without
refreshing your app. However, you can use search facility to locate the map saved. You
can open more than one map at a time.\n\nAdding field notes\n\nAfter capturing the coordinates, one can write filed note by clicking filed notes button.
Viewing map details\n\nAfter creating a KML map file, you can open the same by clicking the file which is saved
in the Mine Mapper folder.\n\nViewing map particulars\n\nYou can view map particulars like coordinates, distance, area, and accuracy of the map
created by clicking the scale icon.\n\nOpening a KML file generated in KOMPAS app\n\nUse KOMPAS software to generate KMZ (zipped KML file) file of the quarry boundary
map. KMZ file can be generated using following Menus:\n1) Mining Entity Master&gt; View
Mining entity or \n2) Mining Entity Location&gt;View in Google Earth or \n3) Mining Entity vs
Concession &gt;Search for quarry &gt; View Google Earth.
When you view the map, you get two options 1) Open with Google Earth and 2) Save
File. Choose Save file. While saving, give the name of the quarry owner to the file you
saved. Email this file to your own Gmail id. Download the attached file into your mobile
phone.\nAfter reaching the quarry location, open the Mine Pillar Mapper App. Load the KMZ file.
Click the pillar icon. You will be able to see the pillar number and co-ordinates.
Mine Mapper App shows the location where you are standing and the coordinates with
accuracy. Open the App. Wait a while for getting maximum accuracy (you may attain an
accuracy of 3-4 m if you wait for a longer period). Keep the Mobile Phone on the top of
the pillar of your interest and check whether your location is falling right on the top of the
pillar in the App. There will be a deviation depending on the accuracy of the GPS
location. If there a deviation in the location, take the screenshot of the screen for future
reference. The screenshot will give you the coordinates of the location of your mobile
phone as well as the deviation.\n\n<b>Compass</b>\n\nBy clicking the Compass icon you can use this app as a professional compass. It may
be noted that the coordinates shown in the Compass screen is the coordinate of the
location at the time of clicking the compass icon.\n\n<b>Navigation</b>\n\nAfter loading a map, when you click the pillar, you can see the coordinates as well as
accuracy. While you click, a navigation button will be seen on the map by clicking which
you can navigate from your current location to that location.\n\n<b>Naming the maps</b>\n\nIf you visit a site and capture the map, then you can name the file by giving applicant’s
name along with file number. The file name as well as date of creation of file will be
shown in the map particulars.\n\n<b>Disclaimer</b>\n\nThis app is developed for helping the Geologists during field work. The accuracy of this
App depends on the accuracy of the GPS of the mobile phone of the user. This App
shall be used for only preliminary verification. Accurate location can be assessed only
using dGPS survey.\n\nPlease send your suggestions/remarks about the App in the Mine Mapper WhatsApp
group\n\nDeveloped by: <b>Biju Sebastian</b> email: bsebastian@gmail.com mobile:
9447310771\n\nMine Mapper 2.0 | © Biju Sebastian
                </justify>
    </string>
</resources>
